(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T00:24:36.697660",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
ATTENTION / Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering is ok.
アニメにハマって歌いたくなっちゃった
Got so into anime, I just had to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて…
Singing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてつらい！
It's almost too precious to handle!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find your favorite anime and game songs!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Sing your favorite song!
JOYSOUND
ReGLOSS 2nd Album「Snapshot」の
ReGLOSS 2nd Album "Snapshot"
レコードとカセットテープが2026年2月25日よりHMV限定で発売決定しました！
will be released exclusively at HMV on February 25, 2026!
12月17日いっぱいまでにご予約いただくと、早期予約特典としてスマホサイズステッカーをプレゼント！
Pre-orders placed by December 17 come with a smartphone-sized sticker!
さらに抽選で5名様様にサイン入りポスターをプレゼント！
Plus, a signed poster for selected winners via lottery!
以上、ReGLOSSでした～！！
That's all from ReGLOSS!!
bangarang bangarang
繁華街 の bunny
Bunny on bustling streets
無数 の 泡 と party yeah
Countless bubbles and a party, yeah
alcohol で fall in'
Falling in with alcohol
週末 崩壊 の 匂い yeah
The scent of a ruined weekend, yeah
the stage is calling . . . rang rang rang
The stage is calling... rang, rang, rang
spotlight 浴び て みな 頭から
Bathed in the spotlight, straight to everyone's head
今夜 ここ だけ server down
Server down right here, tonight
hi！！ show me now , right？
Hi!! Show me now, right?
this song is to cheer you up
somehow , you can't stop thinking about it
Somehow, you can't stop thinking about it
when you 're hurting or feeling down
When you're hurting or feeling down
この先 の 未来 多分 いい 感じ
The future ahead is probably going to be great
super cool どうせ なら 楽しむ yolo
Super cool either way, let's enjoy it, YOLO
hula hoop 逆 に 旋回 し て みな let it go
Spin the hula hoop backwards, let it go
( ha - huh ) we go party sweetest hottest
(Ha-huh) We go party, sweetest, hottest
( ha - huh ) we go party 一旦 騒げ
(Ha-huh) We go party, let's get wild
苦 あり 楽 あり くだらない 坂 は ない
There's no slope without both hardships and fun
飲み干せ energy
Drink up your energy
仲間 たち と swaggin' ey - ey
Swagging with our homies, ey-ey
ハッ と し て 咲かせ 灯せ oh - oh
Suddenly blooming, lighting up, oh-oh
どう なっ て も どうに か なる さ oh - oh yeah
No matter what happens, it'll somehow work out, oh-oh, yeah
come on！！ let 's say！！
Come on!! Let's say!!
that 's what i do when i go all in
That's what I do when I go all in
転がり 落ちたって gonna be alright
Even if you stumble and fall, it's gonna be alright
you 're reaching out your hand
You're reaching out your hand
もう 一度 立ち上がれ ready . . . fight！！
Stand up once more, ready... fight!!
それぞれ の フィールド で yeah
In our respective fields, yeah
物足りない の は 自分 次第
Feeling unsatisfied is up to you
fire up your soul and rise again
何回 何十回 挫けよう とも 火花 散らせ
No matter how many tens of times you falter, let sparks fly
( bangarang bangarang ) 現実 なんて 大体 chaos
(Bangarang, bangarang) Reality is mostly chaos
( bangarang bangarang ) 遊び 尽くし て よ 徹底 的
(Bangarang, bangarang) Play to the absolute limit
( bangarang bangarang ) 楽しん だ もん 勝ち で 語り ましょ う
(Bangarang, bangarang) Let's win by having fun
( bangarang bangarang ) 派手 に let 's survive！！
(Bangarang, bangarang) Let's survive in style!!
yeah yeah yeah
紙細工の花びらを
Paper-crafted petals...
ある人は美しいとつぶやいた
someone murmured that they were beautiful.
この地球の横顔は
What does the profile of this Earth
どう見えてる？キミの世界では
look like in your world?
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down,
失くしそうなモノだけ振り落とした ah
I shook off only the things I was about to lose, ah.
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to pick them up with my palm,
指の隙間すり抜け消えてく
they slipped through my fingers and disappeared.
“形あるものだけが
“Things with form
すべてじゃないけれど
are not everything, but
形あるものが
I want things with form
どうしても欲しいよ”
no matter what.”
この世界を変えることは
Changing this world
きっとできないけれど
I surely cannot do,
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
but if it's the world inside you, I should be able to change it.
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, and withering,
何ひとつ欠かせないから
because not a single thing can be missing.
最後にキミが笑ってくれるなら
If you smile for me in the end,
もうそれだけでいい
that alone is enough.
言葉の綾を紡ぐ人
People who spin the nuances of words,
優しさを編む人
people who knit kindness,
それぞれの正義を
I want to understand
解いてあげたい
each of their justice.
絡まった矛盾と辻褄合わせ
Entangled contradictions and keeping stories straight,
そんな刹那を抱えて今日を生きてる
I am living today while holding onto such fleeting moments.
分け合った灯り 隣から隣へ
Shared light, from neighbor to neighbor,
やがてひとつに 夜の帳へ
eventually becoming one, into the curtains of the night.
息を吹き込んだ
I breathed life into it—
キミとじゃなくちゃだめなんだ ah
it must be you, ah.
このまま寝てしまうには
It was a night wrapped in kindness,
もったいないほど優しさに包まれた夜だった
too wasteful to just fall asleep.
はっきりと浮かび上がった夢の輪郭
Clearly emerged, the contours of a dream;
それは確実に愛だった
that was surely love.
ツキが見守る今夜
Tonight, watched over by the moon,
そっと一瞬を抱き締めた
I gently embraced that instant.
煌めく星
Twinkling stars...
色や形 温度や意味
Color and shape, temperature and meaning,
まるで何もかも違うボクらだけど
even though we are completely different,
きっと最後には
surely in the end
この音で繋がってる
I am connected by this sound.
この世界を変えることは
Changing this world
きっとできないけれど
I surely cannot do,
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
but if it's the world inside you, I should be able to change it.
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, and withering,
何ひとつ欠かせないから
because not a single thing can be missing.
最後にキミが笑ってくれるなら
If you smile for me in the end,
もうそれだけでいい
that alone is enough.
I'll always be by your side
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
本日は ReGLOSS ファーストライブ Flashpointにご来場いただき ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much for attending ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint" today!
Reach the top! We are ReGLOSS!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
おー！
Yeah!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live concert until the very end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
The use of photography, audio, and video recording equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへおしらせください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and notify nearby staff.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに…
Mosh pits, dives, violently jumping up and down, onto the stage—
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Mosh pits, dives, violently jumping up and down, throwing objects onto the stage,
他のみんなの迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
and any actions that inconvenience others or disrupt the performance are strictly prohibited. Please follow the rules and enjoy yourselves!
本公演は、映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Cameras for streaming and photography will be present during the performance, and audience seats may be captured. Please be aware that footage and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
はーい！
Alright!
ライブのハッシュタグは、「ReGLOSSファーストライブ」です。
The live hashtag is #ReGLOSSFirstLive.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag to hype things up!
それでは、開演までもう少々お待ちください！
Now, please wait just a little longer until the show begins!
盛り上がる準備はできてますかー！
Are you ready to get hyped?!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がるぞー！
Let's all get hyped together!
以上、ReGLOSSでしたー！
That's all from ReGLOSS!
紙細工の花びらを
Paper-craft petals
ある人は美しいとぼやいた
Someone murmured that they were beautiful
この地球の横顔は
This side profile of the Earth
どう見えている？
How does it look
キミの世界では
in your world?
現実を逆さにして
Turning reality upside down
失くしそうなものだけ振り落とした ah
I shook off only what I was about to lose, ah
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to pick them up in my palm
指のすき間すり抜け消えていた
They slipped through my fingers and vanished
“形あるものだけが
“It’s not that
すべてじゃないけれど
only things with shape
形あるものが
Are everything, but
どうしても欲しいよ”
I really want something with shape”
この世界を変えることは
I surely cannot change this world
きっとできないけれど
changes are impossible, but
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
you can change the world inside you
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて
Budding, blooming, fruiting, withering
何ひとつ欠かせないから
Not a single part can be missed
最後にキミが笑ってくれたら
If you can smile for me at the end
それだけでいい
That alone is enough
言葉の綯いを紡ぐ人
Someone weaving the strands of words
優しさを編む人
Someone knitting kindness
それぞれの正義を
I want to understand
解いてあげたい
each of their justices
絡まった矛盾と
With tangled contradictions and
辻褄合わせ
coincidences put together
そんな刹那を抱え
Embracing such a fleeting moment
今日を生きてる
I am living today
分け合った灯り
Shared light
隣から隣へ
from neighbor to neighbor
やがてひとつに
Eventually becoming one
夜の帳へ
into the curtain of night
息を吹き込んだ
I breathed life
キミとじゃなくちゃだめなんだ ah
It has to be with you, ah
このまま寝てしまっては
Just falling asleep like this
もったいないほど
is far too wasteful
優しさに包まれた夜だった
A night wrapped in tenderness
はっきり浮かび上がった夢の輪郭
The clearly emerged outline of a dream
それは確かに愛だった
That was certainly love
ツキが見守る今夜
Tonight, watched over by the moon
そっと一瞬を抱き締めた
I gently embraced that moment
煌めく星
Shimmering stars
色や形や温度や意味
Color, shape, temperature, meaning
まるで何もかも違うボクらだけど
We are completely different, but
きっと最後にはこの音で繋がってる
Surely in the end we're connected by this sound
この世界を変えることは
I surely cannot change this world
きっとできないけれど
changes are impossible, but
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
you can change the world inside you
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて
Budding, blooming, fruiting, withering
何ひとつ欠かせないから
Not a single part can be missed
最後にキミが笑ってくれたら
If you can smile for me at the end
それだけでいい
That alone is enough
I’ll always be by your side
Otonose Kanade
Ichijou Ririka
Juufuutei Raden
Todoroki Hajime
漠然とした不安
Vague anxiety,
欲しかった fun
the fun I wanted.
日常に違和感？
A sense of discord in daily life?
うんざりしていた
I was so sick of it.
見慣れたありきたりな眺め
This familiar, ordinary view,
理屈を超える変化を求めていた
I was seeking change beyond reason.
窮屈で退屈な日々の中で
Within these cramped and boring days,
突然キミは現れた
suddenly you appeared.
全身の細胞駆け巡るように
As if coursing through every cell of my body,
走り出した未完成なストーリー
an unfinished story began to run.
モノクロだった景色がいま
The monochrome scenery now
キミと出会いカラフルに彩る
meets you and colors up in full color.
brand new world
ココロ奪われた
My heart was stolen,
気まぐれな瞬間ハートビート
a capricious moment's heartbeat.
揺らぐ時空の狭間
In the gap of swaying spacetime,
もうひとりじゃない煌めく星
a glittering star, no longer alone.
描く未来予想図は
The future projection we draw
同じ夢を引き寄せたいよ
wants to draw the same dream closer.
果てしない旅路の向こうで
Beyond the endless journey,
鳴りやまないロマンが待っている
an unceasing romance awaits us.
my heart starts skipping a beat
紐解いた新章
The newly unfolded chapter
様変わりしてゆく show time
A showtime that keeps changing its look
全然悪くないイマジネーション
An imagination that isn't bad at all
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The fog in my field of vision clears away
悲しみに別れを告げる
And I bid farewell to my sorrow
酸いも甘いも宙に放り出して
I cast aside the bitter and the sweet into the sky
滲む空 インクは薔薇色
The ink bleeding into the sky is rose-colored
どれだけ上手く魅せようとしても (hey!!)
No matter how well I try to show it off (Hey!!)
キミがいなければ何の意味もない
If you aren't here, it has no meaning at all
擦り傷すらつかない幻想 (hey!!)
A fantasy that doesn't even get a scratch (Hey!!)
針の落ちないレコードさ
A record where the needle doesn't drop
たった今 止め処ない追い風にして
Just now, with the endless tailwind at my back
come on, let's roll
芳醇と吹き荒れる
Even against the gusty headwind
向かい風にも
blowing briskly,
ココロ震わせて
I let my heart flutter.
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on to the future
フライングしたって alright
Even if I jump the gun, alright
restart line!! (hey!!)
ときめいてしまえば
Once my heart starts racing
瞬く間に広がる開放区
A liberation zone spreads in an instant
ひとつひとつすべてがドラマ
Every single thing is a drama
待ち侘びた daybreak
The long-awaited daybreak
restart line!! (hey!!)
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
The panorama that colors everything in turn
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
A feeling radiation overflowing
始まりのその時が来た
The beginning, that moment has come
nothing is impossible
マヤカシ誤魔化し効かない世界
A world where deception and trickery don't work
この先はまだ誰も知らない正解
A correct answer that no one knows yet
傍観してるだけじゃ味気ない
It's boring just to stand by and watch
リアルタイムで通い合って
Connecting in real-time
振子にかけるエモーション
Emotion swinging like a pendulum
後の祭りでも i don't mind
Even if it's 'ato no matsuri', I don't mind
大胆不敵な シチュエーション
A bold and fearless situation
行けるところまで行ってみたい
I want to go as far as I can go
選択肢にない get off on the way
Get off on the way, not in the options
共に声を鳴らし
Let's ring out our voices together
素肌を貫くような
Like it's piercing my bare skin
真っ直ぐな痛みが伴っても
Even if it comes with straight pain
この仲間たちと最果てまで
With these friends of mine, to the end of the world
keep running to the end
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on to the future
フライングしたって alright
Even if I jump the gun, alright
restart line!! (hey!!)
ときめいてしまえば
Once my heart starts racing
瞬く間に広がる開放区
A liberation zone spreads in an instant
ひとつひとつすべてがドラマ
Every single thing is a drama
待ち侘びた daybreak
The long-awaited daybreak
restart line!! (hey!!)
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
The panorama that colors everything in turn
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
A feeling radiation overflowing
始まりのその時が来た
The beginning, that moment has come
nothing is impossible
マヤカシ誤魔化し効かない世界
A world where deception and trickery don't work
この先はまだ誰も知らない正解
A correct answer that no one knows yet
飛び出せ you raise me up
Jump out, you raise me up
恐れるものはない
There is nothing to fear
restart line!! (hey!!)
奇麗な朝焼けが
A beautiful sunrise
不透明な明日を照らすよ
Illuminates the opaque tomorrow
restart line!! (hey!!)
皆さん、こんにちは！
Hello everyone!
okey dokey 史上最高な bvdiz
Okey dokey, the greatest bvdiz ever
easy breezy 歌い出せば favorite
Easy breezy, once we start singing, it's our favorite
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey dokey, we want to stay just like this
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody
それぞれ異なった価値観
Each of us has different values
マイナスもプラスになり交わる
Even negatives turn into pluses and intersect
揃えて無理ゲーだって勝ち誇り
Gathering together, boasting we'll win an impossible game
さあ、お決まりの挨拶から始まる
Now, it starts with our usual greeting
愉しみな仲間 気づけば by my side
Cheerful friends, before I knew it, by my side
徒労もアリ 馬鹿騒ぎ
Futile efforts are fine too, making a ruckus
運命共同体 伝染していく喜怒哀楽
Community of fate, our emotions spreading
分かり合えるエンパシー 共に向かうは
Empathy we share, together heading toward
reach the top yeah
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対的ないいキラーチューン
Absolute, absolute, absolute, absolute best killer tune
今は自由気儘 水入らずのユニバース
Now we're free and easy, an intimate universe
reload re reload reload シンクロするシナプス
Reload, re-reload, reload, synapses synchronizing
限界突破 惹きつけるミラクル
Breaking limits, an alluring miracle
okey dokey 史上最高な bvdiz
Okey dokey, the greatest bvdiz ever
easy breezy 歌い出せば favorite
Easy breezy, once we start singing, it's our favorite
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey dokey, we want to stay just like this
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody
みんな！次の曲は満員デイズ！
Everyone! The next song is Manin Days!
盛り上げる準備はいいですかー！
Are you ready to get hyped?!
みんなで大きくドキドキしてねー！
Let's make our hearts race together!
okey dokey 史上最高な bv diz
Okey dokey, the greatest bvdiz ever
easy breezy 歌い出せば favorite
Easy breezy, once we start singing, it's our favorite
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey dokey, we want to stay just like this
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey dokey, we want to stay just like this
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody
誰と誰が手を取って
Whoever takes each other's hands
価値観も雲泥の差で乗り越え笑い合えば
Overcoming worlds of difference in values and smiling together
無限だって勝手なときめきのない明日から始まる
Starting from tomorrow without any selfish excitement
一体何が正解かすら分かんないまま
Without even knowing what the right answer is
夢中で走った
I ran frantically
むちゃ話もひととき
Even crazy talks for a moment
ぱっと花咲かそう
Let's make flowers bloom in a flash
夢中飛行 今日だって テンションして
Frenzied flight, hyped up today too
行く気道 愛の和
The path we walk, the circle of love
分かち合える エルエベース
Sharing it, L.A. base
共にめっさ ソー！
Together, super so!
reach the top yeah
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対的ないいキラーチューン
Absolute, absolute, absolute, absolute best killer tune
今は自由気儘 水入らずのユニバース
Now we're free and easy, an intimate universe
reload re reload reload シンクロするシナプス
Reload, re-reload, reload, synapses synchronizing
限界突破 惹きつけるミラクル
Breaking limits, an alluring miracle
okey dokey 史上最高な bv diz
Okey dokey, the greatest bvdiz ever
easy breezy 歌い出せば favorite
Easy breezy, once we start singing, it's our favorite
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey dokey, we want to stay just like this
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody
ひとり集まれば またひとり
If one person gathers, then another
無性に会いたくなる気持ち
The feeling of wanting to see you so badly
片隅のモノローグも 繋がるプロローグ
Even monologues in the corner connect to a prologue
もう終了時間 あっという間の stream
Already time to end, a flash in the stream
皆といる空間が extreme
The space with everyone is extreme
量産する掛け替え無い memories
Mass-producing irreplaceable memories
遮二無二 掴み取る next dream
Headfirst, grabbing the next dream
運命共同体 伝染していく喜怒哀楽
Community of fate, our emotions spreading
分かり合えるエンパシー 共に向かうは
Empathy we share, together heading toward
reach the top yeah
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対的ないいキラーチューン
Absolute, absolute, absolute, absolute best killer tune
今は自由気儘 水入らずのユニバース
Now we're free and easy, an intimate universe
reload re reload reload シンクロするシナプス
Reload, re-reload, reload, synapses synchronizing
okey dokey 史上 最高な bv diz
Okey dokey, the greatest "bv diz" in history!
easy breezy 歌い出せば favorite
Easy breezy, if you start singing, it's your favorite!
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey dokey, we want to stay just like this, right?
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody!
それぞれ異なった価値観
Each with different values,
マイナスもプラスになり交わる
minus and plus intersect and mingle.
揃えば無理ゲーだって勝負だ
Even if it's an impossible game, we'll take it on!
reach the top yeah
艶やかな仲間の気付けば by my side
Vibrant companions by my side before we knew it,
徒然もアリたまに馬鹿騒ぎ
idle talk is fine, sometimes going wild.
運命共同体 伝えていく喜怒哀楽
A community of destiny sharing joy, anger, sadness, and pleasure,
分かち合えるエンパシー 共に見指すは
empathy we share, what we aim for together is...
reach the top yeah
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対的 キラーチューン
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely a killer tune!
今は自由気まま水入らずなユニバース
Now a free and easy universe without interruption,
reload re reload reload シンクロするシナプス
reload, re-reload, synapses synchronizing,
限界突破 惹き付けるミラクル
breaking limits, attracting miracles!
okey dokey 史上 最高な bv diz
Okey dokey, the greatest "bv diz" in history!
easy breezy 歌い出せば favorite
Easy breezy, if you start singing, it's your favorite!
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey dokey, we want to stay just like this, right?
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody!
いつもの挨拶からいきましょう
Let's start with our usual greeting!
リッチだ ファースト ライブ！ ニグロス！
ReGLOSS First Live! ReGLOSS!
では早速自己紹介からしていきたいと思います！
Now, let's move right along to self-introductions!
輝く輝く笑顔届け！ 儒烏風亭らでん！
Delivering a sparkling, shining smile! Jyuufuutei Raden!
デビュー初めましてのライブ！ メンバー一緒に作ろう！ 儒烏風亭らでんから！
My very first live since debut! Let's make it together with all the members! Starting with Jyuufuutei Raden!
玉座と違って緊張で…
Unlike the throne, I'm so nervous...
みんな温めて！ うれしいよ！
Everyone, warm me up! I'm so happy!
キラキラになってる！ ありがとう！
I'm all sparkly! Thank you!
そして…
And...
可愛いポジティブ！ 轟京子！
Cute and positive! Todoroki Kyoko!
轟かです！ 一度より二度かなよ！
It's Todoroki! Twice is better than once, right?
やばいもうみんなの声めっっちゃこのとも浴びてる今！
Oh gosh, we're soaking up everyone's voices so much right now!
めっっちゃ嬉しい！ ありがとう！ 最高な気分！
We're so happy! Thank you! Best feeling ever!
はい、えー ホロライブデバイシュはリグロスの賑やかシネトーク担当 儒烏風亭らでん でございます 本日はどうぞよろしくお願い申し上げます
Yes, um, Hololive Device is ReGLOSS's lively talk representative, Jyuufuutei Raden. Thank you very much for having us today.
最初は「愛・ブ・ブ・ブ・プライベート・カレンダー・で・し・た・り・ごっ・と・ぱん・ち」！
First was "Ai Bu Bu Bu Private Calendar de Shitari Gotton Panchi!"
続きまして、次はみらたん「こんちくわ！」
Next up is Mira-tan with "Konchikuwa!"
紫咲アリオス調！ ありがとう！ ついに始まりました！
Murasaki Alios style! Thank you! It has finally begun!
リグロス ファースト ライブ！
ReGLOSS First Live!
体重は可哀想！
The body weight is... wait, so cool!
キラキラだな！
So sparkly!
こんなにたくさんのグロッサーが集まってくれました！
So many Reglossers gathered for us!
すごい！ もう最高の景色ですよ、皆さん！
Amazing! This is the best view, everyone!
ありがとう！ 思い思いのね、ファッションとかもね、肉眼で見えてね
Thank you! We can see everyone's outfits with our own eyes, and...
ヒーリングラデーションの時ちょっとテンションが爆上がりしてしまいましたが、本当にありがとうございます！
During the healing gradation, my tension went through the roof, but thank you so much!
今日は最後まで思いっきり楽しんでまいりましょう！
Let's enjoy ourselves to the fullest until the very end today!
そしてね、会場だけじゃなくて配信もされております！
And not just in the venue, but it's also being streamed!
配信の皆さん、楽しんでますかー？
Everyone watching the stream, are you having fun?
イエーイ！ コメント欄もね！
Yay! Check the comment section too!
そしてそして、韓国ではライブビューイングが実施されています！
And what's more, live viewing is being held in Korea!
あんにょん！ あんにょん！ あんにょん！
Annyeong! Annyeong! Annyeong!
ライブビューイングの星子、保護者シーズンの皆さん、楽しく楽しんでご参加ですかー？
To all the live viewing Hoshiko and guardian season viewers, are you having fun participating?
すごーい！ 韓国だぜー！
Amazing! It's Korea!
すごいじゃんやばいよ！ 当たり前だろ！
That's amazing, crazy! Of course!
はい、えーということで早速ですが、今立っているこのステージではなくなんと2階からの登場でございましたが、皆さんびっくりした？どうだった？びっくりした？
Yes, um, with that being said, we actually appeared from the second floor rather than this stage, were you surprised? How was it? Surprised?
びっくりしたー！
Surprised!
オープニングからヒーリングラデーション、そしてBODIESと2曲続けてお披露目させていただきましたが、皆さんいかがでしたかー？
From the opening, Healing Gradation, and then BODIES back-to-back, how did everyone like it?
どうよ？どうよー！
How was it? How was it?!
え、ちゅーちゅーでね、みなさんもうお気づきかっちゃおまえまちけ、ま、今回のライブはバンドメンバーと一緒にお届けしていまーす！
Um, chu-chu, everyone has already noticed... wait, this time's live is delivered together with the live band members!
いつも聴いてるあの曲がどんなアレンジになるのか、お楽しみに！
Look forward to seeing what kind of arrangement those songs you always listen to will have!
はい、えー今日の感想や心に残った瞬間はハッシュタグ「リグロスアンダーバーファーストライブ」でぜひポストしてください！
Yes, um, please post your impressions and memorable moments from today using the hashtag #ReglossUnderbarFirstLive!
みんなの感想あとで我々見に行きますのでめちゃくちゃ楽しみです！よろしくお願いしまーす！
We'll go check out everyone's impressions later, so we're really looking forward to it! Thank you so much!
そしてではございますが、次の曲に行きましょうか？
And with that, shall we move on to the next song?
お、でも待って待って！
Oh, but wait, wait, wait!
ユーチューバーやTikTokで見てくれてる皆さん、ごめんなさい！
To everyone watching us on YouTube and TikTok, I'm sorry!
えっ、早い！だと
It's so fast!
無料チラ見スポットでなんとです、次の客までとなっております！
Free delivery is coming up next!
えー！
Yay!
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたい！みんなは解禁欄のリンクから見てください！
Everyone, let's keep getting more and more excited!
はい！
Please check it out!
うん！
Yay!
みんなちゃん！
Everyone!
ライブはね、まだまだ始まったばかりだぜよ！
Live has only just begun, let's go!
最後までね、一緒に最高の時間を作ろう！
Let's enjoy this to the very end together!
snowfall
触れる上空
Touching the upper air,
幻想と過ぎし
passing by like an illusion,
ノイズは砂嵐
the noise is a sandstorm.
slo-mo
come let me show you
戯れてみせる銀世界
a silver world acting it out,
yeah yeah yeah yeah
if the sky is falling down...
if the stars had no shine...
真っ平らな紙の上
On a blank sheet of paper,
答え滲ませる
letting the answers seep in.
すべて思うままに
Leaving everything to my thoughts,
風が刻む波のmelody
the melody carved by the wind.
pandora pandora
ユメを holding in my heart
holding my dreams in my heart,
移ろい色褪せないように
so that the shifting colors won't fade.
pandora pandora
秘密のオブジェット
a secret object.
skavla
rum pum pum pum pum pum pum pum
snowfall 触れる上空
snowfall touching the upper air,
幻想と過ぎし
passing by like an illusion,
ノイズは砂嵐
the noise is a sandstorm.
slo-mo
come let me show you
戯れてみせる銀世界
a silver world acting it out,
yeah yeah yeah yeah
if the sky is falling down...
if the stars had no shine...
真っ平らな紙の上
On a blank sheet of paper,
答え滲ませる
letting the answers seep in.
すべて思うままに
Leaving everything to my thoughts,
風が刻む波のmelody
the melody carved by the wind.
pandora pandora
ユメを holding in my heart
holding my dreams in my heart,
移ろい色褪せないように
so that the shifting colors won't fade.
pandora pandora
秘密のオブジェット
a secret object.
skavla
rum pum pum pum pum pum pum pum
灯す光 the sign of sprouting
the illuminating light, the sign of sprouting.
skavla
ワンクール回のドラマよりも
More than a one-cool drama,
永い fairy tale
an eternal fairy tale.
嘘偽りなく take this pain
Take this pain without any falsehood.
匙を投げた plastic mind
A plastic mind that threw away the key.
この世に表も裏もない
In this world, there is no surface or reverse,
いつも違う表情 曇れない irony
an irony with ever-changing expressions.
一日を抱き締めたいのに
Even though I want to embrace the whole day,
沈む足跡
sinking footprints.
怯む暇はない 上を目指そう
There's no time to hesitate, let's aim for the top.
in a world where no one's hurt,
i might not have become kind
忍ばせて、仮初
Holding it in, playing innocent,
朽ちるまで待ち焦がれ
waiting and yearning until it rots,
いずれ花になる
eventually turning into a flower.
風が刻む波のmelody
the melody carved by the wind.
pandora pandora
ユメを holding in my heart
holding my dreams in my heart,
移ろい色褪せないように
so that the shifting colors won't fade.
pandora pandora
秘密のオブジェット
a secret object.
可能性が swirling in a dance
Possibilities are swirling in a dance,
幾重にも重なって
overlapping in layers,
たゆたう歪に ambivalence
drifting into a distorted ambivalence.
振り解いたその向こう風
Beyond what was shaken off, the wind blows.
rum pum pum pum pum！！
rum pum pum pum pum!!
今こそ切な願い 打ち鳴らせ wake up
Now is the time, let's make this earnest wish ring out, wake up.
そっと手を伸ばす 冬枯れの結晶
Gently reaching out a hand to the winter-withered crystals.
閉じ込めてしまいそうな夜だって
Even on a night that feels like it's going to close us off,
この歌声で繋ぎとめてみせるから
because I'll connect and bind it together with this singing voice.
skavla
rum pum pum pum pum pum pum pum
灯す光 the sign of sprouting
the illuminating light, the sign of sprouting.
skavla
rum pum pum pum pum pum pum pum
象る star
resembling a star.
skavla
rum pum pum pum pum pum pum pum
紙細工の花びらを
Papercraft petals...
ある人は美しいとぼやいた
Some murmured that they were beautiful.
この地球の横顔は
What does the profile of this Earth
どう見えているの？キミの世界では
look like in your world?
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down,
失くそうとモノだけ振り落とした ah
I shook off everything I was about to lose, ah.
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to pick them up in my palms,
指の隙間すり抜け消えてた
they slipped through my fingers and vanished.
“形あるものだけが
"Things with form aren't
すべてじゃないけれど
everything, but still,
形あるものが どうしても欲しいよ”
I desperately want things that have form."
この世界を変えることは きっとできないけれど
I probably can't change this world,
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
but I should be able to change the world inside you.
芽吹いて 咲いて 実って 枯れて
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, withering—
何ひとつ欠かせないから
not a single thing can be missed,
最後にキミが笑ってくれたら
so if you smile at the very end,
もうそれだけでいい
that alone is enough for me.
言葉の綾を紡ぐ人
Those who spin wordplay,
優しさを編む人
those who weave gentleness—
それぞれの正義を 解いてあげたい
I want to unravel their respective justices.
絡まった矛盾と 辻褄合わせ
Tangled contradictions and reconciliation,
そんな刹那を抱え 今日を生きている
embracing such fleeting moments, we live today.
分け合った灯り
A shared light,
隣から隣へ
from neighbor to neighbor,
やがてひとつに 夜の帳へ
eventually becoming one, into the veil of night.
息を吹き込んだ
Breathing life into it—
キミとじやないとだめなんだ ah
it has to be with you, ah.
このまま寝てしまうには もったいないほど 優しさに包まれた夜だった
It was a night wrapped in too much warmth
to simply fall asleep like this.
はっきり浮かび上がった夢の輪郭
The outline of a dream clearly emerged;
それは確実に愛だった
that was undoubtedly love.
ツキが見守る今夜
Tonight, watched over by the moon,
そっと一瞬を抱き締めた
I gently held that fleeting moment close.
煌めく星
Gleaming stars...
色や形 温度や意味
Colors and shapes, warmth and meaning,
まるで何もかも違うボクらだけれど
we are as if completely different in every way,
きっと最後には この音で繋がっている
yet surely in the end, we are connected by this sound.
この世界を変えることは きっとできないけれど
I probably can't change this world,
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
but I should be able to change the world inside you.
芽吹いて 咲いて 実って 枯れて
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, withering—
何ひとつ欠かせないから
not a single thing can be missed,
最後にキミが笑ってくれたら
so if you smile at the very end,
もうそれだけでいい
that alone is enough for me.
i'll always be by your side
♪
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました。
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.